have2have.co.za 2008-06-16

# Have2Have Online Store

### Privacy

 **Have2Have respects your privacy.**

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

Private Customer information (credit cards, S.S. Numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days. (If a company requires more than 60 days, they must receive special approval from Trust Guard.)

Customer will not receive any continual email solicitation from the company, unless the customer consents to the solicitation at checkout, or through a double opt-in process. And, if the customer does consent to receive email from the company, the company agrees to have a simple unsubscribe option available, along with unsubscribe instructions in every email.

 **Credit card details**

Your credit card info is stored for the purposes of billing, and is securely stored and fully encrypted to the latest most secure industry standard

 **External Sites.**

Have2Have is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

 **Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Have2Have to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Have2Have does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

 **Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Have2Have and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Have2Have have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:info@have2have)
